A Guide to the Albemarle Garden Club Papers
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #5520-f
Albemarle Garden Club Papers 1938-1987
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
5520-f
550 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was loaned to the University of Virginia Library by the Albemarle Garden Club on October 29, 1987
Container List
- Albemarle Garden Club: Material from files used for a history, 1938-1981
- Albemarle Garden Club: Minutes, 1971-1981
- Albemarle Garden Club: Morea(court suit), 1983-1984
- Albemarle Garden Club: Reports--Committees, 1941-1972; (2 folders)
- Albemarle Garden Club: Reports--President and Treasurer, 1943-1970
- Albemarle Garden Club: Reports--State and National Clubs, 1950-1974
- Albemarle Garden Club: Yearbooks and Roberts Rules of Order, 1941, 1945
- Garden Club of America: Annual Meetings Programs, 1953-1980; (2 folders)
- Garden Club of America: Handbook and Miscellaneous, 1979-1982
- Garden Club of America: Handbook and Supplement, 1977
- Garden Club of America: Presidents' Reports, 1979-1982
- Garden Club of America: Zone VII, 1971-1983
- Garden Club of Virginia: Annual Meetings Programs, 1976-1980
- Garden Club of Virginia: Annual Presidents' Reports, 1949-1982; (5 folders)
- Garden Club of Virginia: Board of Governors' Meetings, 1976-1982; (2 folders)
- Garden Club of Virginia: Register, 1987